Guide to the Media Services records, [ca. 1950-2015.]
Media Services records, [ca. 1950-2015]
- Series IV. Videotapes
  - Subseries IVa. Videotapes transferred from Distributed Learning Services
    - SH1- 1. From the Depths, 2. Slow Waltz with Dogs, 3. Rachmaninov, 4. Kurt Weill Tango, 5. Piazzolla Tango, 6. Human Fly, 7. Jablkon I, 8. Jablkon II, 9. Mahler, 10. Blues Traveller, 11. Zappa - Bows, CD-632; CD-R (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - Antigone, produced by E. TV. Ctr., CIT, 2004; DVD-560; DVD-R (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - Antigone, 3D Rehearsal Segment, September 3, 2003; V-5251; DVC: 2.5"x3.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - [Antigone] M, V-5252; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - Antigone, Full Performance Dub Master, January 23, 2004; V-5253; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - Antigone, Layoff for LBX, June 2, 2004; V-5254; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - Antigone, Performance for DVD, June 17, 2004; V-5255; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - Making of Antigone: Masks Excerpt, V-5256; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - Making of Antigone: Masks Excerpt (Revised), V-5257; Beta 6.1"x3.8" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - Antigone (Parts I-II), V-5258 - V-5259; Beta 10.4"x6" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - GOV'T 161, Isaac Kramnick, camera original (1), January 22, 2008; V-5260; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - GOV'T 161, Kramnick Course (2), January 24, 2008; V-5261; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - GOV'T 161, Prof. Kamnick, Audio channel 1 only, noise on CH 2, work order #27073 (3), January 29, 2008; V-5262; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - GOV'T 161, Isaac Kramnick, cam. Original, #27075 (4), February 5, 2008; V-5263; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - Isaac Kramnick, Hollis Auditorium, GS, GOV'T, work order 27076 (5), February 7, 2008; V-5264; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - GOV'T 161, Issac Kramnick, Goldwin-Smith Hollister Aud., cam. Orig. (6), February 12, 2008; V-5265; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - GOV'T- Isaac Kramnick, Goldwin-Smith Hollis Auditorium (7), February 14, 2008; V-5266; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - Isaac Kramnick, GOV'T, Goldwin-Smith Hollis Auditorium (8), February 19, 2008; V-5267; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - GOV'T, Goldwin-Smith Hollis Auditorium, Isaac Kramnick (9), February 21, 2008; V-5268; DVC- DV180 (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - GOV'T- Isaac Kramnick, Goldwin-Smith Hollis Auditorium (10), February 26, 2008; V-5269; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - Isaac Kramnick, GOV'T, Goldwin-Smith Hollis Auditorium, #27096 (11), February 28, 2008; V-5270; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - GOV'T- Isaac Kramnick, Goldwin-Smith Hollis Auditorium (12), March 4, 2008; V-5271; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - GOV'T- Isaac Kramnick, Goldwin-Smith Hollis Auditorium (13), March 11, 2008; V-5272; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - GOV'T- Isaac Kramnick, Goldwin-Smith Hollis Auditorium (14), March 13, 2008; V-5273; DVC- DV180 (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - Kramnick-GOV'T 161, HEC Auditorium, Goldwin-Smith, #27083 (15), March 25, 2008; V-5274; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - GOV'T- Isaac Kramnick, Goldwin-Smith Hollis Auditorium (16), March 27, 2008; V-5275; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - GOV'T- Isaac Kramnick, Goldwin-Smith Hollis Auditorium (18), April 3, 2008; V-5276; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - GOV'T- Isaac Kramnick, Hollis Auditorium, Goldwin-Smith Hall (19), April 8, 2008; V-5277; DVCPRO DP121-126L (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - GOV'T- Isaac Kramnick, Hollis Auditorium, Goldwin-Smith Hall (20), April 10, 2008; V-5278; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - GOV'T 161, I. Kramnick Lecture, cam #1, cam original, #27088 (21), April 15, 2008; V-5279; DVCPRO DP121-126L (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - GOV'T 161, Kramnick, cam orig. #27089 (22), April 17, 2008; V-5280; DVCPRO DP121-126L (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - GOV'T 161, Isaac Kramnick, Goldwin Smith- Hollis Auditorium (23), April 22, 2008; V-5281; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - GOV'T- Isaac Kramnick, Hollis Auditorium, Goldwin-Smith (24), April 24, 2008; V-5282; DVCPRO DP121-126L (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - GOV'T- Isaac Kramnick, Hollis Auditorium, Goldwin-Smith Hall (25), April 29, 2008; V-5283; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - GOV'T- Isaac Kramnick, Hollis Auditorium, Goldwin-Smith Hall (26), May 1, 2008; V-5284; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - SOTP, 2 discs, April 30, 2007; DVD-561 - DVD-562; DVD-R (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - SOTP, May 2, 2007; DVD-563; DVD-R (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - SOTP- Weber, 2 discs, April 20, 2007; DVD-564 - DVD-565; DVD-R (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - SOTP- Lubehenco, 2 discs, April 23, 2007; DVD-566 - DVD-567; DVD-R (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - unidentified, DVD-568; DVD-R (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - State of the Planet, From Pres. Of Stanford Don Kennedy, cam orig. #25239, January 24, 2007; V-5285; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - State of the Planet, Per Pinstrup-Anderson, #25249, January 29, 2007; V-5286; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - State of the Planet, Ross M. Welch, camera orginal #25250, January 31, 2007; V-5287; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - State of the Planet, Water Lecture, Rebecca Schneider, camera orginal, #25251, February 5, 2007; V-5288; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - State of the Planet, Jac Geurts, cam orig. #25252, February 7, 2007; V-5289; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - State of the Planet, Stuart Hart, camera orginal, #25253, February 12, 2007; V-5290; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - State of the Planet, David Hammer, camera original #25254, February 14, 2007; V-5291; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - State of the Planet, Zellman Warhaft #25255, February 19, 2007; V-5292; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - State of the Planet, Paul McEven, camera orginal, #25256, February 21, 2007; V-5293; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - State of the Planet, Eric Cheyfitz, camera original #25257, February 26, 2007; V-5294; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - State of the Planet, Tam Eisner, #25258, February 28, 2007; V-5295; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - State of the Planet, Harry Greeve, cam orig. #25259, March 5, 2007; V-5296; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - State of the Planet, John Fitzpatrick-Lab of O. Dir, cam. Orig. #25260, March 7, 2007; V-5297; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - State of the Planet, panel with 3 guests, cam. Orig. #25261, March 12, 2007; V-5298; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - State of the Planet, Laura Harrington, cam orig, #25262, March 14, 2007; V-5299; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - State of the Planet, Art DeGaetano, cam orig, #25263, March 26, 2007; V-5300; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - State of the Planet, Mary Lou Zeeman, cam orig, #25264, March 28, 2007; V-5301; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - State of the Planet, WO# 25265, April 2, 2007; V-5302; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - State of the Planet, Davin Wippman, WO# 25266, April 4, 2007; V-5303; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - State of the Planet, Panel: Barbar Mink, Tom Eisner, Cathy Klimaszewski, Steve Pond, "Activism in Art" #25268, April 11, 2007; V-5304; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - State of the Planet, Tom Eisner, camera original, #25270, April 18, 2007; V-5305; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - State of the Planet, Jane Lubchenco, WO# 25271, April 23, 2007; V-5306; DVC: 3"x4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - State of the Planet, Eco Village, Liz Walker, #25272, April 25, 2007; V-5307; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - State of the Planet, Student Projects, WO# 25273, April 30, 2007; V-5308; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - State of the Planet, Tom Gibrieu, camera original, #25275, March 9, 2007; V-5309; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - State of the Planet, Richard Baer, cam. Orig. WO# 25276, March 2, 2007; V-5310; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - State of the Planet, Katy Payne, February 16, 2007; V-5311; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - State of the Planet, Lecture, Undergrad. Student panel discussion, camera original, #25397, February 23, 2007; V-5312; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - State of the Planet, John Dewitt, WO# 25419, March 30, 2007; V-5313; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - State of the Planet, "Wrap up," Eisner/Zeeman, May 2, 2007; V-5314; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - State of the Planet, Kurt Goddfreed, Nuclear Power, Nuclear Weapons, April 16, 2007; V-5315; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - State of the Planet, speaker: Ted Lowi, April 6, 2007; V-5316; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - State of the Planet, Weber, April 20, 2007; V-5317; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
    - State of the Planet, Andy Zepp, April 9, 2007; V-5318; DVC: 3"X4.9" (Box 35-14-3773 - 78)
- Series V. Audiovisual Catalogs
  - Films, Recordings, Slides, 1950s (Box 21-36-2566 - 35, Folder 1)
  - Audio Visual Catalog, 1987-1988 (Box 21-36-2566 - 35, Folder 2)
  - Audio Visual Resource Center Catalogs-Child Development, Nutrition, Health (Box 21-36-2566 - 35, Folder 3)